PHILIP HOLY

Greenville, SC | 864-346-7874 | philipmholy@gmail.com

PROFILE

Driven software developer with 6 years of experience in a professional environment. At my core, I'm a person in constant pursuit of truth. Proven ability to adapt and excel amidst change. Passion for accuracy and excellence. Self-starter who can work efficiently on a team or as an individual. I'm a man of my word, and I'll put in the time to deliver the results critical for your business operations.

EXPERIENCE

Flocknote

Web Developer Jun 2020 – Present

- Collaborated to design and build an in-house payments product, allowing 400+ organizations to raise >\$14MM for the causes they care about. This includes Credit Card and ACH payment processing, text-to-give, pledge tracking, recurring payments, and EOY tax statements.
- Implemented a Mailchimp API integration, allowing the marketing team to keep track of customer data and send automated email campaigns.
- Designed a notification processor for phone number orders. This involved registering a webhook to hit a serverless
 function (AWS Lambda), which subsequently put notifications into a SQS queue. This approach allowed us to pause or
 throttle notification handling, and preserved data in case of unexpected downtime.
- Built numerous custom reports compiling data from multiple data sources (MySQL database, Elasticsearch, 3rd party APIs). This allowed our sales and customer support teams to access data such as real-time sales projections and feature usage reports.

Shareworks by Morgan Stanley

Systems Analyst/Migration Specialist

Mar 2019 - Jun 2020

- Developed numerous end-to-end ETL pipelines, allowing 100+ companies to smoothly migrate their data onto the Shareworks platform. I also refactored some Pentaho pipelines into faster and more maintainable Python pipelines.
- Wrote Python validation scripts which compared the data of distinct data sources and formats. These tests ensured
 data integrity and peace of mind for our clients.
- Fixed numerous bugs in production data (Oracle SQL), ensuring data integrity and a smooth user experience for end users.

EDUCATION

Mount Angel SeminaryMount Angel, ORMaster of DivinityAug 2015 - May 2016

Newman Theological College Edmonton, AB Master of Divinity Sep 2014 - Jun 2015

University of AlbertaEdmonton, ABB.A. PhilosophySep 2012 - Apr 2015

Degree awarded with distinction

Texas A&M University
Computer Engineering

College Station, TX
Aug 2009 - May 2011

ADDITIONAL

Technical Skills: Advanced in SQL, PHP, Python, Git, Docker, Unit and Integration testing (PHPUnit and Pest), and JetBrains IDEs (IntelliJ, PHPStorm). Proficient in AWS DevOps (EC2, RDS, Route 53, S3, SES, SQS, and more), Linux Sys Admin, HTML, CSS, Javascript, React.js, Bash scripting, Elasticsearch